William S. Rosecrans Papers
William S. Rosecrans Papers,
- Framed etching of General Rosecrans, Added January, 1982.
Box 38, folders 22A, 23, 29, 117
Box 43, folder 125
Box 52, folder 1
Post, Philip S. (Letter from) Box 12, folder 15A
Potomac, Army of the Box 7, folder 140
Box 9, folder 37
Price, Hiram (Letter to) Box 52, folder 3
Price, Rodman M. (Letter from) Box 37, folder 120
Price, Sterling (Mention of) Box 7, folder 128
Box 10, folders 36-105, passim
Box 46, folders 123, 126-131, 133-135
Box 47, folders 2-12, 17
Box 53, folders 88-89, 93-96
Box 54, folder 79
Box 59, folders 55, 117-118, 120
Box 66, folder 115
Box 81, folder 5
Box 86, folder 9
Prime, Frederick E. (Letters from) Box 2, folder 156
Box 3, folders 1, 24, 39
Prime, Frederick E. (Mention of) Box 59, folders 3, 37
Providence, Rhode Island (Harbor improvement at, 1853-1855) Box 3, folders 35-111, passim
Box 4, folder 106
Box 5, folder 134
Pugh, Thomas K. (Letters from) Box 41, folders 40, 90, 102, 105, 125
Pugh, Thomas K. (Letters to) Box 48, folders 76-77, 81, 86, 90-92, 96, 99
Pugh, Thomas K. (Mention of) Box 35, folder 31
Box 76, folder 8
Purcell, John B. (Letters from) Box 1, folder 97
Box 5, folder 119
Box 6, folders 59, 125
Box 8, folder 45
Box 15, folder 3
Box 69, folders 22, 108
Box 78, folders 76, 84
Purcell, John B. (Mention of) Box 35, folder 31
Box 76, folder 8
Quantrill, William C. (Mention of) Box 10, folder 2
Quimby, Isaac F. (Letters from) Box 2, folders 72, 112
Rains, George W. (Letters from) Box 1, folders 31, 51, 48, 82
Rains, George W. (Mention of) Box 44, folder 4
Ralston, William C. (Letter from) Box 11, folder 46
Ralston, William C. (Letter to) Box 50, folder 3
Rancho Canada del Corral, Santa Barbara County, California Box 28, folder 128
Rancho Centinella, Los Angeles County Box 28, folder 18
Box 54, folders 15-16
Rancho El Cajon, San Diego County, California Box 11, folder 118
Box 60, folders 72-73, 77A-79
Box 71, folder 56
Rancho San Juan Del Rio, Mexico Box 12, folder 65
Rancho Sausal Redondo, Los Angeles County Box 11, folders 107, 109, 120, 122-125
Box 12, folders 1, 4, 7, 39, 68, 74, 77, 81, 91, 128, 146
Box 14, folders 8, 15, 68
Box 15, folders 7, 45
Box 16, folders 3,9, 22, 78, 123, 160
Box 17, folders 85, 134, 148, 168
Box 18, passim
Box 19, folders 17, 30, 60, 115, 143
Box 20, folders 27, 34, 37, 40, 56
Box 21, passim
Box 22, folders 61, 103
Box 26, folders 67, 99
Box 27, folders 29, 84
Box 47, folder 51
Box 53, folders 109, 126, 129
Box 54, folders 28, 32-33, 41, 46-47, 60, 62-63, 66, 90, 92, 98
Box 64, folders 75, 77
Box 78, folders 1A-2 (11 letters)
Box 97
Rancho Tajauta, San Bernardino County, California Box 97, folders 1, 10
Rand, Addison C. (Letter from) Box 35, folder 19
Randall, Samuel J. (Mention of) Box 43, folder 55
Randolph, Theodore F. (Printed speech by) Box 87, folder 7
Rawlins, John A. (Letter from) Box 10, folder 100
Rawlins, John A. (Letters to) Box 44, folders 46-47
Box 45, folders 12, 19, 24-25, 34-36, 42-43, 65-66, 75, 83-84, 93-95, 97, 106
Box 49, folders 2, 5
Rawlins, John A. (Mention of) Box 14, folder 56
Read, Thomas B. (Letters from) Box 11, folder 2
Box 69, folder 43A
Box 77, folder 67
Red River Campaign, 1864 Box 9, folder 131
Redemptorist Fathers Box 2, folder 64
Reid, Whitelaw (Letters from) Box 9, folders 6, 10, 160
Box 16, folders 8, 20, 23
Box 17, folders 43, 51, 70
Box 26, folder 147
Box 33, folder 33A
Box 36, folder 20
Box 43, folders 28, 30
Reid, Whitelaw (Letters to) Box 49, folder 6
Box 51, folder 3 (2 letters)
Box 52, folder 3 (2 letters)
Reid, Whitelaw (Mention of) Box 21, folder 64
Box 32, folders 60, 79, 161
Box 47, folder 29
Reynolds, John F. (Letter to) Box 44, folder 8
Reynolds, John F. (Mention of) Box 5, folder 134A
Reynolds, Joseph J. (Letters from) Box 1, folder 42
Box 8, folder 70
Reynolds, Joseph J.(Letters to) Box 49, folder 6 (2 letters)
Reynolds, Joseph J. (Mention of) Box 7, folder 39
Reynolds, William F. (Letters from) Box 1, folder 28
Box 5, folder 154
Rich Mountain, West Virginia, Battle of, 1861 Box 35, folders 47, 104
Box 59, folders 8, 33
Rich Mountain, West Virginia, Battle of, 1861 (Confederate manuscript map of Laurel Hill fortifications) Box 124, folder 6
Richards, Joseph H. (Letter from) Box 43, folder 82
Ripley, Tennessee (Military operations at, October 7, 1862) Box 7, folders 119-120
Riva Palacio, Mariano (Letters from) Box 25, folder 53
Box 26, folders 168-169
Roberts, Marshall O. (Letters from) Box 16, folder 119
Box 20, folder 96
Rodman, Thomas J. (Letters from) Box 1, folders 4, 6, 9
Rodman, Thomas J.(Letter to) Box 44, folder 4
Rodman, Thomas J. (Mention of) Box 1, folder 14
Rollins, James S. (Letter from) Box 24, folder 44A
Romero, Matias (Letters from) Box 12, folders 127, 129-130, 131, 140, 142
Box 14, folders 65, 73, 75, 79, 85, 87, 89-91, 100, 112, 115-116, 123, 126-127
Box 15, folders 1, 8-9, 17, 37, 59, 68, 79, 95, 100, 113, 127
Box 16, folders 11, 30, 43, 126-127, 165
Box 17, folders 10, 22-23, 25-26, 33, 44, 50, 105, 131
Box 18, folders 16, 109, 126
Box 19, folders 77, 106
Box 20, folders 1, 29, 50, 123
Box 21, folder 85
Box 23, folders 29, 93
Box 32, folder 163
Box 33, folder 77
Romero, Matias (Letters to) Box 47, folders 98, 108
Box 49, folders 5 (2 letters), 6 (11 letters)
Box 50, folders 1 (4 letters), 2 (2 letters), 3 (4 letters)
Box 51, folder 2
Box 52, folder 1
Romero, Matias (Mention of) Box 15, folders 11, 29, 41, 54
Box 16, folder 44
Box 17, folder 49
Box 20, folder 80
Roosevelt, Theodore (Letter from) Box 77, folder 84
Rosecrans, Adrian L. (Correspondence) Box 63, folders 1-32
Box 64, folders 56-61
Box 71
Box 75, folders 51-54
Box 77, folders 1-70
Box 78, folders 42-45
Rosecrans, Adrian L. (Writing and memorabilia of) Box 107, folders 1-3
Rosecrans, Adrian L. (Mention of) Box 10, folder 136
Box 11, folders 23A, 51
Boxes 31-117, passim
Box 35, folders 47, 104
Rosecrans, Ann Eliza (Hegeman) (Correspondence) Box 52, folder 3 (2 letters)
Boxes 55-62
Boxes 69-76
Rosecrans, Carl F. (Correspondence) Box 63, folders 81-124
Box 64, folders 63-68
Box 73, folders 51-67
Box 75, folders 56-62
Box 77, folders 6-9, 71
Box 78, folders 36, 38, 46-52
Rosecrans, Carl F. (Memorabilia) Box 107, folders 1-3
Rosecrans, Sylvester H. (Correspondence) Box 49, folders 5 (3 letters), 6
Box 65, folders 84-121
Box 66
Box 76, folders 1-38
Box 77, folders 53-63,65
Box 78, folders 56-67, 80-85
Rosecrans, Sylvester H. (Writings and memorabilia) Box 107, folders 6-9
Rosecrans, Sylvester H. (Mention of) Box 1, folders 81, 83, 94, 97, 113
Box 14, folder 63
Box 34, folders 104-136, passim
Box 35, folder 47
Box 65, folders 11, 13-15
Box 70, folder 52
Box 71, folder 67
Rosecrans Victory March (Music by Charles Crosby) Box 80, folder 27
Ross, Leonard F. (Letter to) Box 7, folder 87
Rousseau, Lovell H. (Letters from) Box 8, folder 71
Box 10, folder 57
Ryan, Patrick J. (Letters from) Box 10, folder 133
Box 34, folder 118A
Ryder, James (1800-1860) (Letter from) Box 1, folder 83
Sacred Heart of Jesus (Activities of the group of Army officers devoted to, organized by Rosecrans) Boxes 2-4, passim
Box 6, folder 2
Safety Powder Company, San Francisco Box 34, folders 90, 120
Boxes 35-36, passim
Box 48, folders 33, 35, 114
Box 54, folders 51-53, 58
Box 62, folders 112-114
Box 63, folders 72, 110-116
Box 64, folder 74
Box 67, folder 26
Box 72, folders 53,55,60
Box 73, folder 60
Box 77, folder 71
Box 98
Sage, Ebenezer (Mention of) Box 78, folder 90
St. Augustine, Florida (Spanish fortifications at) Box 1, folder 36
St. Louis (General Rosecrans welcomed by citizens of, 1864) Box 9, folder 73
St. Louis (Military and religious affairs in, 1850) Box 2, folder 56B
San Diego & Gila Southern Pacific & Atlantic Railroad Company Box 11, folders 10, 20, 37, 6
Box 12, folders 102, 107
Box 14, folders 28, 47
Box 15-16, passim
Box 17, folders 22, 60A
Box 18, folder 116
Box 19, folder 114
Box 20, folders 68, 122
Box 21, folders 42, 50-51, 74
Box 22, folder 28
Box 24, folders 37, 78, 80
Box 25, folders 60, 139
Box 26, folder 138A
Box 27, folders 29, 84
Box 61, folders 20-90, passim
Box 66, folder 121
Box 96, folders 2, 4
San Diego & Los Angeles Railroad Company Box 17, folder 151
Box 19, folder 158
Box 53, folder 123
Box 96, folder 5
San Diego, California (Defenses) Box 11, folder 6
San Diego, California (Fort Yuma wagon road to) Box 14, folder 28, 33
San Diego, California (Pueblo lands) Box 11, folder 50
Box 14, folder 33
San Diego, California (Railroad routes to) Box 11, folders 47, 52, 54, 62-63, 68-69
Box 15, folder 48
San Diego, California (Real estate development) Box 11, folder 53, 58
Box 12, folder 76
Box 14, folders 28, 33
Box 15, folder 64
Box 22, folder 20
San Francisco (Business activities in) Box 12, folder 128
San Francisco (Earthquake of Oct. 2, 1868) Box 12, folder 128
San Francisco (Fortifications at) Box 3, folders 25, 30
San Francisco (Real estate speculation in) Box 11, folder 60
San Francisco & Colorado Railroad Company Box 24, folders 37, 78
San Francisco Examiner (James W. Oates's qualifications to serve on editorial staff of) Box 37, folder 71
San Francisco Examiner (Possible purchase of by J.C. Flood to make it a Democratic organ) Box 37, folder 16
San Francisco (steamship) (Wreck of) Box 4, folder 30
San José Mine, Egan Canyon, Nevada Box 19, folder 154
Boxes 28-37, passim
Boxes 20-28
Box 61, folder 94
Box 62, folder 109 passim
Box 94
Sanderson, John P. (Letter from) Box 10, folder 21
Sanderson, John P. (Letter from) Box 10, folder 21
Santa Barbara County, California (Sheep raising in) Box 11, folder 48
Santa Catalina Island, Los Angeles County (Mining on) Box 27, folder 138
Santa Clara Valley Railroad Company Box 31, folders 9, 93
Santa Cruz Island, Santa Barbara Company, California (Sheep raising on) Box 11, folder 48
Santa Monica, California (Gold mining on beach at) Box 40, folders 74, 92
Box 41, folder 5
Santo Domingo Ranch and Mines, Chihuahua, Mexico Boxes 36-38, passim
Box 39, folders 65, 89-90, 107, 120
Box 40, folder 49
Box 41, folder 34A
Box 48, folders 31-107, passim
Box 54, folder 60
Box 62, folder 14
Box 93, folders 14-20
Sargent, Aaron A. (Letter from) Box 32, folder 135
Sargent, Aaron A. (Letters to) Box 50, folder 2
Box 51, folder 1
Satterlee, Richard S. (Letter from) Box 3, folder 70
Savage, Richard H. (Letter from) Box 39, folder 51
Scammon, Charles M. (Mention of) Box 77, folder 26
Scammon, Eliakim P. (Letters from) Box 1, folders 60, 86-87, 89A-90
Box 2, folders 2, 9, 13A, 141
Box 12, folder 131A
Box 15, folder 24
Box 33, folder 5
Box 34, folder 116
Scammon, Eliakim P. (Mention of) Box 5, folder 153
Box 6, folder 55
Box 76, folder 13
Scammon, Jonathan Y. (Letters from) Box 6, folders 84, 120
Scammon, Jonathan Y. (Mention of) Box 58, folder 90
Schell, Augustus (Letter to) Box 52, folder 3
Schenck, Robert C. (Letters from) Box 16, folders 100-101
Box 18, folder 128
Box 19, folder 131
Schenck, Robert C. (Letters to) Box 50, folder 1
Box 51, folder 3
Schenck, Robert C. (Mention of) Box 10, folder 22
Box 12, folder 89
Box 19, folder 133
Box 55, folders 68, 73
Box 61, folder 21
Box 66, folder 108
Schofield, John M. (Letters from) Box 8, folder 5
Box 18, folder 119
Box 30, folders 100, 102, 110-111, 114-116
Box 53, folder 64
Box 69, folder 115
Box 78, folder 22
Box 81, folder 20
Schofield, John M. (Mention of) Box 8, folder 16
Box 9, folder 44
Box 32, folders 65, 70
Box 39, folder 2A
Box 56, folder 57
Schriver, Edmund (Letter from) Box 9, folder 72
Scott, Irving M. (Letters to) Box 51, folder 4
Box 54, folder 73
Scott, John (1824-1896) (Letter from) Box 26, folder 102
Scott, John N. (Letters from) Box 36, folders 95A-B
Scott, Thomas A. (Letters from) Box 16, folder 156
Box 17, folder 117
Box 19, folder 3
Box 53, folder 140
Box 90, folder 9
Scott, Thomas A. (Letters to) Box 47, folder 8
Box 49, folder 6
Box 50, folders 1 (3 letters), 2 (2 letters)
Box 51, folders 3, 4
Box 52, folder 1
Box 69, folder 85
Scott, Thomas A. (Mention of) Box 17, folders 5, 53, 118, 130, 138, 147, 171
Box 18, folders 3, 55-58, 62, 86
Box 19, folders 7, 39, 70, 146, 152
Box 20, folder 36, 42, 75, 77,95, 116
Box 21, passim
Box 22, folders 28, 70, 79, 109
Box 24, folders 37, 78
Box 25, folders 42, 60, 66, 71, 137, 139
Box 26, folders 49, 67, 137
Box 27, folders 29, 84, 126, 170
Box 47, folder 64
Box 61, folders 30-31
Box 68, folders 112-113
Scott, Winfield (Mention of) Box 1, folders 47, 82
Box 2, folders 54A, 61, 82, 88
Box 12, folder 53
Sedgwick, Thomas S. (Letters from) Box 11, folders 68, 108
Box 12, folders 49, 77-78, 87, 93, 99, 107
Box 14, folder 13
Box 15, folders 43, 81, 87, 112, 130, 135
Box 16, folders 12, 109, 112, 143
Box 17, folder 91
Box 19, folder 137
Box 20, folders 28, 79
Box 25, folder 60
Box 31, folder 65
Sedgwick, Thomas S. (Letters to) Box 49, folder 6 (4 letters)
Box 50, folders 1 (5 letters), 3
Box 51, folder 1
Sedgwick, Thomas S. (Mention of) Box 20, folders 68, 75, 110, 116
Box 21, folder 51, 68
Seward, William H. (Document signed by) Box 124, folder 14
Seward, William H. (Letters from) Box 16, folder 157
Box 17, folders 2, 112, 118, 124, 138
Box 20, folder 128
Seward, William H.(Letters to) Box 17, folder 71
Box 47, folders 62, 74
Box 49, folder 2
Box 50, folders 1 (4 letters), 2
Seward, William H. (Mention of) Box 10, folder 24
Box 12, folder 103
Box 15, folders 117-120, 123, 127
Box 16, folders 1, 39, 42, 91
Box 17, folders 139, 147, 160
Box 18, folders 3, 16
Box 18, folders 3, 16
Box 32, folder 144
Seymour, Horatio (Letters from) Box 12, folders 46, 55
Seymour, Horatio (Letters to) Box 44, folder 13
Box 47, folder 50
Seymour, Horatio (Mention of) Box 8, folder 147
Box 12, folder 57
Box 61, folder 9
Shaffner, Taliaffero P. (Mention of) Box 47, folder 29
Sheridan, Philip H. (Letters from) Box 8, folder 72
Box 43, folder 33
Sheridan, Philip H. (Letters to) Box 46, folder 15
Box 51, folder 4
Box 52, folder 3
Sheridan, Philip H. (Mention of) Box 9, folder 106
Box 59, folder 46
Box 86, folders 6, 9
Sherman, William T. (Letters from) Box 9, folder 107
Box 10, folder 93
Box 16, folder 102
Box 19, folder 138
Box 32, folders 136-137, 149
Box 34, folder 98
Box 49, folder 2 (2 letters)
Sherman, William T. (Letters to) Box 49, folders 2, 6
Sherman, William T. (Mention of) Box 3, folder 59
Box 5, folder 134A
Box 7, folders 16-17, 21
Box 8, folder 23
Box 21, folders 10, 98
Box 30, folder 97
Box 34, folder 14
Box 38, folder 129A
Box 40, folder 133
Box 56, folder 35
Box 57, folder 8
Box 59, folders 39, 43, 115
Box 60, folder 10
Box 61, folder 65
Box 62, folders 35, 40
Box 63, folder 25
Box 66, folder 100
Box 71, folder 133
Box 81, folder 20
Box 86, folder 6
Shields, James (1806-1879) (Letter from) Box 26, folder 88
Shields, James (1806-1879) (Mention of) Box 2, folders 99, 109
Shiloh, Battle of, 1862 Box 21, folder 98
Shiras, Alexander E.(Letter to) Box 49, folder 6
Simonton, James W. (Letter from) Box 18, folder 137
Simonton, James W. (Letter to) Box 50, folder 2
Sitgreaves, Lorenzo (Mention of) Box 2, folder 164
Skilton, Julius A. (Letters from) Box 17, folder 153A
Box 18, folders 12, 67, 72
Slocum, Henry W. (Mention of) Box 8, folder 133
Smith, Andrew J. (Mention of) Box 10, folders 36, 40-41, 90, 94-95, 97-98
Box 59, folder 39
Smith, Caleb B. (Letter from) Box 53, folder 10
Smith, Giles A. (Letters from) Box 16, folders 81, 76
Smith, Gustavus W. (Letter from) Box 1, folder 45
Smith, Gustavus W. (Mention of) Box 2, folder 38
Smith, Henry L. (Mention of) Box 3, folder 109
Smith, Joseph (1790-1877) (Letter from) Box 3, folder 122
Smith, Martin L. (Letters from) Box 1, folders 1, 10-11, 29, 32, 36, 52
Box 69, folder 1
Smith, Richard (b. 1823) (Letter from) Box 10, folder 174
Smith, William F. (Letters from) Box 35, folder 87
Box 54, folder 49
Smith, William F. (Letters to) Box 51, folder 2 (4 letters)
Smith, William F. (Mention of) Box 10, folder 4
Sonora Railroad Concession (Mexico) Box 20, folders 57, 74-75, 89
Box 26, folders 49, 137
Box 33, folders 75, 84, 101, 127B, 130-131, 139
Box 34, folders 8A, 23, 33-34, 77, 137
Box 35, passim
Box 36, folder 47
Box 37, folders 4-5, 26, 58
Box 42, folder 99
Box 53, folder 130
Box 54, folders 13, 92
Sorin, Edward F. (Letter from) Box 10, folder 136
Southern Pacific Railroad Company Box 12, folders 77, 102
Box 20, folders 92, 98, 105, 113, 116
Box 21, folder 17
Box 23, folders 35, 70-73
Box 24, folder 36
Box 26, folders 67, 93, 103
Box 27, folders 29, 84, 163, 170
Box 31, folder 4
Box 34, folder 102
Box 37, folder 118
Box 39, folder 9
Box 41, folder 86
Box 69, folder 112
Box 96, folder 1
Southern Transcontinental Railroad Box 17, folders 99, 102, 113
Box 19, passim
Box 20, folder 60
Southwest Railroad Box 100, folder 150
Sparks, William A.J. (Letter from) Box 40, folder 94
Spaulding, Martin J. (Letter from) Box 5, folder 80
Spofford, Ainsworth R. (Letter to) Box 52, folder 1
Sprague, John T. (Letter from) Box 8, folder 147
Sprague, John T. (Mention of) Box 3, folder 71
Sprague, William (1830-1915) (Letters from) Box 21, folder 128
Box 22, folders 54, 81
Sprague, William (1830-1915) (Letter to) Box 50, folder 3
Box 51, folder 2
Squire, Watson C. (Letter from) Box 30, folder 98
Squire, Watson C. (Letter to) Box 51, folder 4
Stager, Anson (Letters from) Box 21, folders 110-111
Stager, Anson (Mention of) Box 42, folder 95
Stahel, Julius (Letter from) Box 22, folder 52
Stanford, Leland (Letters from) Box 19, folder 29
Box 26, folder 83
Box 41, folder 106
Stanford, Leland (Letters to) Box 47, folder 86
Box 48, folder 97
Box 50, folders 1, 2
Stanford, Leland (Mention of) Box 17, folders 18, 32, 42, 46, 89, 144
Box 19, folders 86, 155-156
Box 20, folders 43, 67
Box 21, folders 41, 53
Box 22, folder 103
Box 23, folders 35, 70
Box 24, folder 37
Box 26, folders 67, 93
Box 27, folders 29, 34, 84, 170
Box 28, folder 118
Box 31, folder 51
Box 33, folder 94
Box 34, folder 102
Box 61, folders 19, 44, 69
Box 69, folder 112
Stanley, David S. (Letters from) Box 7, folders 66, 92-95, 110, 113-114, 129
Box 8, folders 73, 132
Stanley, David S.(Letters to) Box 44, folders 38, 49, 78-83, 113-114, 122-123, 125, 136
Stanley, David S. (Mention of) Box 7, folders 72, 104, 111-113
Box 38, folder 129
Box 59, folder 54
Stanton, Edwin M. (Document signed by) Box 124, folders 7, 11
Stanton, Edwin M. (Letters from) Box 7, folder 59
Box 8, folders 54, 59, 86, 110
Box 9, folder 97
Box 10, folders 15, 45
Box 49, folder 2 (2 letters)
Box 53, folder 68
Stanton, Edwin M. (Letters to) Box 45, folders 50, 52, 76, 110, 113, 118, 131
Box 46, folders 18, 91, 94, 100, 103
Box 49, folder 2
Box 53, folders 83, 117
Stanton, Edwin M. (Mention of) Box 8, folders 9, 45A
Box 9, folders 1, 29, 37, 148
Box 10, folders 26, 50, 156, 160, 180
Box 37, folder 12
Box 38, folder 136
Box 39, folder 113
Box 43, folders 13, 18, 54, 125
Box 46, folder 80
Box 48, folders 36, 111
Box 59, folders 2, 30, 107
Box 61, folder 10
Box 66, folder 62
Box 76, folder 19
Box 16, folder 9
Stearns, Abel (Mention of) Box 11, folder 56, 58
Stearns, George L. (Letter to) Box 47, folder 32
Stearns, George L. (Mention of) Box 8, folders 104, 107
Steedman, James B. (Letter from) Box 38, folder 112
Steele, Frederick (Letters from) Box 10, folders 55, 106
Box 53, folders 93-94, 96
Steele, Frederick (Mention of) Box 10, folder 112
Stephens, Alexander H. (Letter from) Box 12, folder 32
Stephens, Alexander H. (Mention of) Box 12, folder 57
Stetefeldt, Carl A. (Letter from) Box 30, folder 74
Stetefeldt Furnace Company, San Francisco Box 30, folder 84
Box 95, folders 13-14, 25
Stevens, Isaac I. (Letters from) Box 2, folders 82, 89, 92, 94, 108, 110, 114-115, 117, 144, 155
Box 3, folders 6, 15, 19, 20-21, 30
Stevens, Isaac I. (Mention of) Box 2, folder 119
Box 3, folder 67
Stevens, Walter H. (Letters from) Box 2, folders 4, 7, 13, 16A, 27, 40
Box 3, folders 7, 16
Stockton & San Joaquin Canal Company Box 18, folder 116
Stone, Charles P. (Letters from) Box 7, folders 13, 17, 21
Stone River, Battle of, 1862-1863 See: Murfreesboro, Battle of, 1862-1863
Stoneman, George (Letters from) Box 8, folderss 10, 34
Stoneman, George (Mention of) Box 61, folder 91
Box 63, folder 115
Straus, Adolph D. (Letters from) Box 17, folder 48
Box 25, folder 54
Stuart, Alexander H.H. (Letter from) Box 12, folder 32
Stuart, James E.B. (Mention of) Box 80, folder 25
Sumner, Charles (Letters from) Box 17, folder 68
Sumner, Charles(Letters to) Box 47, folder 75
Box 49, folders 5 (2 letters), 6 (2 letters)
Sumner, Charles (Mention of) Box 14, folder 49
Box 61, folder 2
Sutter, John A., Jr. (Letters from) Box 14, folder 58
Box 15, folder 30
Sweetser, Charles (Letter from) Box 2, folder 123
Swinton, William (Letter from) Box 15, folder 91
Sykes, George (Letter from) Box 10, folder 87
Szabad, Emeric (Letter from) Box 16, folder 74
Taft, William H. (Mention of) Box 54, folder 86
Taunton River, Massachusetts (Survey of, 1852-1853) Box 2, folders 150, 163
Box 3, folders 48, 50, 62, 64, 93, 102-103, 107, 112-113
Box 58, folder 54
Tawney, James A. (Printed speech by) Box 87, folder 28
Taylor, Moses (Letters from) Box 20, folders 12, 16
Taylor, Moses (Letters to) Box 50, folder 3
Taylor, Zachary (Mention of) Box 5, folder 29
Box 65, folder 81
Tehuantcpec, Isthmus of (Canal across projected) Box 18, passim
Box 19, folder 46
Box 20, folder 127
Tehuantcpec, Isthmus of Box 19, folder 105
Box 32, folder 8
Teller, Henry M.(Letters to) Box 52, folder 3 (2 letters)
Tennessee, Society of the Army of the: Box 82, folder 2
Tenure of Office Act - Senate debates on repeal of, 1869: Box 14, folder 29
Tevis, Lloyd (Mention of) Box 17, folders 42, 46, 138, 156
Box 26, folders 67, 97
Box 27, folder 29
Box 69, folder 112
Texas (Annexation of) Box 1, folder 52
Texas (In the Mexican War) Box 2, folders 28, 54A
Texas (Railroad construction in, 1872) Box 23, folder 44
Texas (Rosecrans' scheme for promotion of immigration to) Box 18, folders 5, 18, 65, 69, 75, 113
Box 19, folders 16, 21, 23-26, 37, 134
Texas & Pacific Railroad Company Box 17-21, passim
Box 22, folders 1, 70, 79, 109
Box 23, folder 69
Box 24, folders 37, 78, 80, 95
Box 25, folders 63, 139
Box 26, folders 67, 91, 93, 160
Box 27, folders 31, 126
Box 28, folder 62
Box 117, folders 29, 108
Box 33, folder 94
Box 36, folder 68
Box 53, folder 144A
Box 68, folders 40-43
Box 96, folders 9, 16
Texas Gulf & Pacific Railroad Company Box 96, folder 12
Thayer, Sylvanus (Letters from) Box 2, folder 129
Thébaud, Augustus J. (Letters from) Box 1, folders 81, 94, 113
Thomas, George H. (Letters from) Box 8, folders 74, 166
Box 9, folder 20
Box 10, folders 88, 94, 130
Box 11, folder 12
Box 49, folder 2
Thomas, George H. (Letter to) Box 46, folder 78
Thomas, George H. (Mention of) Box 2, folder 54B
Box 9, folders 3, 106
Box 10, folders 4, 84-85, 89-90, 93, 95-98
Box 14, folder 36
Box 17, folders 16, 30
Box 19, folders 2, 6, 11, 19, 34-35, 73
Box 21, folder 3
Box 22, folder 75
Box 43, folder 79l
Box 47, folders 77, 90
Box 48, folders 36, 111
Box 55, folder 71
Box 59, folder 43
Box 66, folder 61
Box 68, folder 12
Box 81, folder 20
Box 86, folder 6
Thomas, John A. (Letter from) Box 2, folder 35
Thomas, Lorenzo (Letters from) Box 8, folder 41
Thomas, Lorenzo (Letters to) Box 45, folders 7, 98, 123, 126, 129, 133-135, 138
Box 46, folders 19, 29, 31, 33, 71-73, 75, 105, 113
Box 47, folder 38
Box 49, folders 2 (8 letters), 5 (2 letters)
Thomas, Lorenzo (Mention of) Box 47, folder 64
Thompson, Richard W. (Mention of) Box 62, folder 101
Thomson, John E. (Letters from) Box 11, folder 123
Box 21, folder 84
Box 25, folders 21, 79
Box 90, folder 9
Thomson, John E. (Letter to) Box 47, folder 47
Thurman, Allen G. (Letters from) Box 15, folder 4
Box 53, folder 112
Thurman, Allen G. (Mention of) Box 35, folder 47
Box 78, folder 85
Thurston, Gates P. (Letters from) Box 11, folder 65
Box 40, folder 56
Tilden, Samuel J.(Letter to) Box 52, folder 1
Tilden, Samuel J. (Mention of) Box 117, folder 39
Tod, David (Letter from) Box 8, folder 20
Tod, David (Letters to) Box 45, folders 11, 107
Torbert, Alfred T.A. (Letters to) Box 51, folders 2, 3 (2 letters)